# **Noval Dwi Putra**

## PHP DEVELOPER / BACKEND DEVELOPER

+(62) 899-2652-281

nvldwiptr@gmail.com

movaldwp.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/noval-dwi-putra

3+ years experience in web applications development using PHP framework (such as Codelgniter and Laravel) and JQuery. Have sufficient experience regarding system design, database design, ERD/UML, and communication skills. Looking for job opportunities to apply the skills I have, even better if there are new skills to learn and apply.

### Work Experience

#### PHP Developer (Freelancer)

Desember 2020 - Present

- Build efficient and reusable PHP function.
- Implement code based on project specifications.
- Integrated third-party API such as RajaOngkir, Midtrans and Digiflazz to complete the task.
- Ensured that all work complied established standards and guidelines.

#### PHP Developer

CV. Internal Media, Kalibata, Jakarta Selatan | March 2019 - November 2020

- Build and developing application using Codelgniter Framework and MySQL database.
- Creating web pages for user interfaces using HTML, Bootstrap, and JQuery.
- Learn to build application programming interfaces (API) and develop them using Codeigniter Framework.
- Participate in building user experiences, aiming to make it easier for users to operate the application.
- Participate in building or modifying database design.
- Ensured that all work complied with client established standards and guidelines.
- Learn and migrate Content Management System (CMS) from Codelgniter using Laravel Framework.

#### PHP Developer (Internship)

CV. Internal Media, Kalibata, Jakarta Selatan | October 2018 - January 2019

- Learn Codelgniter Framework from PHP programming language.
- Learn HMVC Design Pattern using CodeIgniter Framework.
- Build Web Application using CodeIgniter Framework.
- Support other developers to development programs.

#### **Technical Skills**

- Server-side: PHP (with Laravel and Codelgniter Framework). Passive in GoLang and NodeJS.
- Client-side: HTML, Bootstrap, JQuery, VueJS.
- Databases: MySQL. Passive in MongoDB.
- Collaborations: Git, Trello, Agile and Scrum.
- Tools: VSCode, Laragon and Postman. Passive in Docker.

#### **Education**

• Bachelor's Degree Computer Science at STMIK Jakarta STI&K.